export const javascriptQuestions = [
    {
      question: "Which is different from other regarding to javascript?",
      options: ["Number", "String", "Float", "Boolean"],
      correctOption: 2,
      points: 10
    },
    {
        question:"What are the different data types in JavaScript?",
        options:["Number", "String", "Boolean", "All"],
        correctOption:3,
        points:10
    },
    {
        question:"What is hoisting in JavaScript?",
        options:[
            "The process of moving declarations to the top of their scope.",
            "when variable access before declaration is hoisting",
            "when variable declaration in function and access out side of function",
            "Using function an other function"
        ],
        correctOption:0,
        points:10
    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following statement(s) is true about the JavaScript?",
        options:[
            "It is a scripting language used to make the website interactive",
            "It is an advanced version of Java for Desktop and Mobile application development",
            "It is a markup language of Java to develop the webpages",
            "All of above Answer"
        ],
        correctOption:0,
        points:10
    },
    {
        question:"In which HTML element, we put the JavaScript code?",
        options:[
            "<javascript>...</javascript>",
            "<script>...</script>",
            "<js>...</js>",
            "<css>...</css>"
        ],
        correctOption:1,
        points:10
    },
    {
        question:"Which symbol is used separate JavaScript statements?",
        options:[
            "Comma (,)",
            "Colon (:)",
            "Hyphen (_)",
            "Semicolon (;)"
        ],
        correctOption:3,
        points:10
    },
    {
        question:"JavaScript ignores?",
        options:["newline", "tabs", "space","All of the above"],
        correctOption:3,
        points:10
    },
    {
        question:"Which is the correct syntax to call an external JavaScript file in the current HTML document?",
        options:[
            "<script src=jsfile.js></script>",
            "<script href=jsfile.js></script>",
            "<import src=jsfile.js></import>",
            "<script link=jsfile.js></script>",

        ],
        correctOption:0,
        points:10
    },
    {
        question:"Which JavaScript method is used to call a function (a callback function) once for each array element?",
        options:[
            "for()",
            "traverse()",
            "forEach()",
            "foreach()"
        ],
        correctOption:2,
        points:10
    },
    {
        question:"Which is/are the valid JavaScript method(s) to extract string parts?",
        options:[
            "A.	slice(start, end)",
            "B.	substring(start, end)",
            "C.	substr(start, length)",
            "D.	All of the above"
        ],
        correctOption:3,
        points:10
    },
    {
        question:"Which is the correct JavaScript statement to define string as object?",
        options:[
            "A.	var s = new String('IncludeHelp!');",
            "B.	var s = String('IncludeHelp!');",
            "C.	var s = 'IncludeHelp!'",
            "D. All of the above"
        ],
        correctOption:0,
        points:10
    },

]
// {
//     ,
//   {
//     question: "What triggers a UI re-render in React?",
//     options: [
//       "Running an effect",
//       "Passing props",
//       "Updating state",
//       "Adding event listeners to DOM elements"
//     ],
//     correctOption: 2,
//     points: 20
//   },
//   {
//     question: "When do we directly \"touch\" the DOM in React?",
//     options: [
//       "When we need to listen to an event",
//       "When we need to change the UI",
//       "When we need to add styles",
//       "Almost never"
//     ],
//     correctOption: 3,
//     points: 20
//   },
//   {
//     question: "In what situation do we use a callback to update state?",
//     options: [
//       "When updating the state will be slow",
//       "When the updated state is very data-intensive",
//       "When the state update should happen faster",
//       "When the new state depends on the previous state"
//     ],
//     correctOption: 3,
//     points: 30
//   },
//   {
//     question: "If we pass a function to useState, when will that function be called?",
//     options: [
//       "On each re-render",
//       "Each time we update the state",
//       "Only on the initial render",
//       "The first time we update the state"
//     ],
//     correctOption: 2,
//     points: 30
//   },
//   {
//     question: "Which hook to use for an API request on the component's initial render?",
//     options: ["useState", "useEffect", "useRef", "useReducer"],
//     correctOption: 1,
//     points: 10
//   },
//   {
//     question: "Which variables should go into the useEffect dependency array?",
//     options: [
//       "Usually none",
//       "All our state variables",
//       "All state and props referenced in the effect",
//       "All variables needed for clean up"
//     ],
//     correctOption: 2,
//     points: 30
//   },
//   {
//     question: "An effect will always run on the initial render.",
//     options: [
//       "True",
//       "It depends on the dependency array",
//       "False",
//       "In depends on the code in the effect"
//     ],
//     correctOption: 0,
//     points: 30
//   },
//   {
//     question: "When will an effect run if it doesn't have a dependency array?",
//     options: [
//       "Only when the component mounts",
//       "Only when the component unmounts",
//       "The first time the component re-renders",
//       "Each time the component is re-rendered"
//     ],
//     correctOption: 3,
//     points: 20
//   }
// }